<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Making By Markdown </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/markdown_syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/markdown_syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post_3/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hey there,&#xA;I’m Gowra Pavan Kumar, a fourth-year IT student at Kallam Haranadhareddy Institute of Technology in Guntur, Andhra Pradesh.&#xA;I’m passionate about tech and love diving into programming languages like C and Python. I’m also into web development, playing around with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build cool stuff online.&#xA;Through my blog, I want to share what I’ve learned and help others explore the exciting world of technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Developer Virtual Internship</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/intern-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/intern-one/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1: EXECUTIVE SUMMARY Learning Objectives: Understand the Salesforce Platform Architecture. Develop Salesforce Objects and Fields Using Apex Code. Design and Implement Visualforce Pages for Custom User Interfaces. Integrate Salesforce Applications with External Systems. Deploy and Secure Salesforce Applications. Learning Outcomes: Understand the key components of the Salesforce platform. Write Apex code to create and manage Salesforce objects. Build custom user interfaces using Visualforce. Consume external data using the Salesforce APIs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> NARAYANA JR. COLLEGE BRUNDAVAN GARDEN GUNTUR</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/inter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/inter/</guid>
      <description>About NARAYANA JR. COLLEGE BRUNDAVAN GARDEN GUNTUR NARAYANA JR. COLLEGE BRUNDAVAN GARDEN GUNTUR was established in 2012 and it is managed by the Pvt. Unaided. It is located in an Urban area within the GUNTUR block of GUNTUR district, ANDHRA PRADESH. The school offers Grades 11 to 12 and is Co-educational. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have an attached pre-primary section. The school is not using a school building as a shift-school. English is the medium of instruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Kondabolu Lakshmi Prasad Public School, Guntur</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/school/</guid>
      <description>About Dr. Kondabolu Lakshmi Prasad Public School, Guntur Dr. Kondabolu Lakshmi Prasad Public School, also known as Dr. KLP Public School, was established in 1983. It is managed by the Nagarjuna Education Society. The school is affiliated with the Central Board of Secondary Education (CBSE).&#xA;School Information Year of Establishment 1983 School Area 12485 Sq. Metres Parent Institution Nagarjuna Education Society Academics Affiliation: CBSE Streams Offered: PCM, PCB &amp;amp; Arts Medium(s) of Instruction: English Classes: Nursery to 12th Gender: Co-Ed Residential Status: Boarding School No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>intern 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/intern-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/intern-1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
